picnicnetwork.org 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Picnic!

Your privacy is important to us. It is Picnic’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.picnicnetwork.org/, and other sites we own and operate.

We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.

We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

### Advertising

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/94152), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/94149) may also be used to serve ads on your site, which should also be disclosed in your privacy policy in the following manner:

  * Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.
  * Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.
  * Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

This policy is effective as of 4 March 2019.
